<?xml version="1.0"?>

<!-- Definition of Category Instrumentation and photography -->

<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
         xmlns:skos="http://www.w3.org/2004/02/skos/core#">


    <skos:Concept rdf:about="http://mydomain.com/subjects/instrumentation+and+photography#">

        <skos:definition>Includes remote sensors; measuring instruments and gages; detectors; cameras and photographic supplies; and holography. For aerial photography see 43 Earth Resources and Remote Sensing. For related information see also 06 Avionics and Aircraft Instrumentation; and 19 Spacecraft Instrumentation.</skos:definition>

        <skos:prefLabel xml:lang="en">instrumentation and photography</skos:prefLabel>
        <skos:altLabel xml:lang="en">instrumentation</skos:altLabel>
        <skos:altLabel xml:lang="en">imaging</skos:altLabel>

        <skos:editorialNote>Exhaustive: Design, development, installation, and use of devices for detecting, measuring, recording, telemetering, processing, or analyzing values or quantities related to aeronautical or space flight; the environment within or outside the flight vehicle; the physical operation and well being of the flight vehicle and its structure during all phases of flight; the facilities for testing and/or developing the flight vehicle; the observations and experiments performed as a result of the flight of these vehicles;
                  Selective: Instrument design, development, and theory for other purposes that have potential aerospace applications because of advanced or unusual features, or are developed for extreme environments or unusual test conditions;
                  Negative: Commercial off-the-shelf photographic equipment and instrument design and development for general use for artistic or commercial applications.</skos:editorialNote>

        <skos:broader rdf:resource="http://mydomain.com/divisions/engineering#"/>

        <skos:exactMatch rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/page/Instrumentation"/>
        <skos:related rdf:resource="http://dbpedia.org/page/Sensor"/>
        <skos:related rdf:resource="http://rdf.freebase.com/ns/en.sensor"/>
        <skos:related rdf:resource="http://rdf.freebase.com/ns/en.optical_telescope"/>

        <skos:related rdf:resource="https://www.freebase.com/m/01j7cq"/> <!-- sensor -->
        <skos:related rdf:resource="https://www.freebase.com/m/01ngsz"/> <!-- optical telescope -->

    </skos:Concept>

</rdf:RDF>
